In 1868 Longhorn Texas, a convicted outlaw had two
choices: get hung, or get married.
Goin' South is a comedy, western, romance film directed by Jack Nicholson.
Henry Moon is captured for a capital offense by a posse when his
horse quits while trying to escape to Mexico.
He finds that there is a post-Civil War law in the small town that any single
or widowed woman can save him from the gallows by marrying him.
Henry Moon, played by Jack Nicholson.
Julia Tate, played by Mary Steenburgen.
Towfield, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Hector, played by John Belushi.
Hermine, played by Veronica Cartwright.
Sheriff Kyle, played by Richard Bradford.
Goin' South is a 1978 American western comedy film directed by and starring Jack Nicholson, with Mary Steenburgen,
Christopher Lloyd, John Belushi, Richard Bradford, Veronica Cartwright, Danny DeVito and Ed Begley Jr.
The film explores themes of small town, texas,
anti hero, dark comedy, gold rush.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.